[
  {
    "question": "I ___ a student.",
    "correct": "am",
    "choices": ["am", "is", "are", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "He ___ my brother.",
    "correct": "is",
    "choices": ["are", "am", "is", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You ___ very kind.",
    "correct": "are",
    "choices": ["is", "are", "am", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "She ___ from Canada.",
    "correct": "is",
    "choices": ["am", "are", "is", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We ___ friends.",
    "correct": "are",
    "choices": ["is", "am", "be", "are"]
  },
  {
    "question": "They ___ at home.",
    "correct": "are",
    "choices": ["are", "is", "am", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "She and I ___ classmates.",
    "correct": "are",
    "choices": ["is", "am", "be", "are"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It ___ a sunny day.",
    "correct": "is",
    "choices": ["are", "am", "is", "be"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and he ___ good friends.",
    "correct": "are",
    "choices": ["am", "is", "be", "are"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I ___ not tired.",
    "correct": "am",
    "choices": ["are", "is", "be", "am"]
  }
]

